yo yo Scopus alright so we are we are we
are doing it we are putting the
ultra-rare my job okay
so let's wait for a few people to get in
here but maybe we'll post this periscope
on slack someone want to do it so we
want to post that in kama we're doing
the merge drop guys we're doing the
merch table but before we do the merge
drop down on the hoodies no no no that
he's no hoodies let's not get crazy yeah
okay
no no no she's
the first thing I'm going to show you is
our flow nets like we were making flow
nest
look at the flow net it kind of works
this was trained unsupervised and
unsupervised machine learning kind of
works kind of works it has a little
trouble getting a road down here
sometime but I went to the diner on
Saturday and I read papers and I read
flow papers and then implemented this
flow paper no it's not decent it's bad
look see how the road drops out we're
trying to fix that we're using the
uncompressed videos but ya know you'll
see it's like it's pretty good when
there's like a car coming the other way
now they're getting the flow but like
all of this flow here is missing yeah so
red means it's going that way and green
is the vertical flow see it works there
when there's actual texture on the road
um yeah we'll see maybe we'll get a car
coming the other way but guys know the
flow that's not we're here to talk about
you know what we're here to talk about
the exclusive limited merge drop so Yun
flipping put the mapping yeah it doesn't
work well on flat textual services well
roads aren't really textualist we think
of the uncompressed ones we can get it
but guys let me show you the limited
edition comma AI beanies right here so
equal is on track to be comma a eyes
highest revenue month in history you
know more than we announced pandas more
than more than ever more than the
self-driving car awareness tour and
really it is it is thanks to you guys I
know it's April it's almost over we have
to make 1000 more dollars worth of sales
so that's one yawn but also we can make
some money selling the hoodie so selling
these beanies so let's see how many we
have we have one we have two we have I'm
gonna turn you guys sideways okay I know
I know you might get crazy here alright
hang on why didn't that
rotate no unlock like that will count
the beanies together so that's a to
beanies over here three no hoodies well
well that was a mistake for be nice
I've but you get beanies okay you told
Kent hoodies six beanies and then this
here is my personal beanie which I'm not
selling I'm gonna put it on my head
right now they're really warm and cozy
we have two softest merch in the game
now the second softest I can't I still
don't know if I could say that but look
okay guys all right so here we are on
our Shopify back-end well okay let's not
get too crazy here comma can you pick up
no no no no no we don't do that we will
ship these out on Monday beanie
exclusive limited only six all right
okay guys so what should we well no no
we're just dropping mercs today that's
all we're doing all right so if you here
for the merch drop you here for a merge
drop and so how should we describe the
beanie guys don't have any good words we
need words
black that's good word I like that black
it goes on your head your head
Oh midnight black oh no no that's that's
trademarked for aeons very black oh very
black will definitely add that too yeah
I love the super hearts by the way guys
we're gonna become a paid Paris copy
soon very black up it goes on your head
has a comma let's put that on the next
line we don't make this is for souls of
all colors a beanie has no holes that's
a good point has a comma on it
topologically it has no holes I'm not
sure about animals I don't think
anywhere harmed but I can't state that
topologically has no oh no typing with
one hands heart no pulse
okay cool you may be more gangster if
you wear I got to qualify that with men
you just I got more gangster if you wear
it micro holes aren't holes holes
not yes oh can I say blockchain powered
is that legal
something-something b-baby I don't know
if I can say that something something I
can definitely say something something
that's legal does not use lighter light
are not included include it or need it
[Laughter]
what is the merge cop
it's the Kama AI beanie we only have six
of them I looked around the office at
first I thought it was only four but
then I found two more so there's six
brand-new Kamiya beanies right here ah
one more thing can hold o let's see if
we can put a neon in a beanie oh that
sounds fun
alright so here we have a neon and let's
see if it fits in the beanie it does it
fits in the beanie and let's try to put
this Panda in here too oh that's good
that's good oh yeah good holder for your
comment AI hardware good older for your
it does not come with a panda or no I
shouldn't say that that sounds like
something that can be bad compatible
with humans well someone's gonna buy
this beanie so we shouldn't you know
leave my card
Panda right there check out that panda
by the way this stuff's all and I'm shop
a comedy I make sure to check it out
alright guys so we know how many we have
in stock this is a physical product
what's the weight event point three
pounds let's say inventory policy
Shopify tracks this products inventory
six allow customers to purchase product
when it's out of stock no that's it
there is only six of them I will be
uploading an image shortly I'm sorry you
look dumb in a beanie clay but we are
only offering beanie so guys this is the
big question will be scanned by the Aeon
nobody's writing that code ok cool guys
what should the price be this is
exclusive much we got to remember that
throw some numbers out there $20 this is
exclusive merch 500 dollars that's a
little much 150 that's a little 1,000
over six that's that's more doable 399
how many exists well so I have one here
for my head and then I have six up for
sale alright alright alright alright
about 25 will free shipping is always
included except for International
shipping guy you have to pay 30 there's
six ever yeah I mean there's no
guarantees of that that's just how many
I found $99 you guys what can we
actually price it at oh ah you know what
we're gonna go with 69 let's go at $69
[Laughter]
only six the price is $69 off let's save
this product I want to make sure I don't
little look over here while shop with my
loads because I can't show you any
secrets view all right let's go all
right guys it's black who wants to buy
it
Skokie thinks that price is
inappropriate the prices all be going up
guys just because I'm pricing beanies
$69 this is exclusive comedy I'd merch
exclusive limited it's still cheaper
than jeeva yay that's what I'm saying
right oh we should say compare just do
you want Chang have a beanie let's let's
look at the G Vaughn che beanie
oh my god $279 Wow okay alright so I'm
gonna say compared at price 270 how much
was that again
275 damn compare at price 275 compared
to that's probably illegal I could say
compared to that's legal we did nice I
love it I love it
guys this really there's only six of
these okay compared to this beanie it's
[Music]
ile of a life time um okay well you know
what I think we just sold one so I
actually think we actually did just sell
one so I think the price is about to go
up you're not seeing it guys it's posted
and slack okay guess what someone bought
one guess what the price the next be
Gnaeus $79 prices went up now it's 79
early I back in the day we were just
talking about that actually do this
beanie yeah look at that
we might be dropping the price back to
69 I don't know if we should do this so
you see that we have 15 outstanding
orders right now so when I can refresh
this page I believe and it won't show
any secrets
wait oh my god we have 20 outstanding
orders right everyone just buy I'm not
showing you guys the $79 no there's
literally one left when someone buys it
you'll see it go to out of stock you
know what I'm not gonna do that they're
all gonna be the last one gets it for 79
that's
you should you should have gotten Harley
should come in quick
oh forget it we gotta sell one more
beanie guys wait okay know what to sell
one more beanie I'm gonna post it on
Twitter top that exclusive merch
there's literally one left and now the
price is $79 it might have sold out like
literally you guys are crazy
oh no it didn't put the product photo we
did a product photo wait okay do we sell
the last beating up no one's buying the
last beanie
we're so five we haven't sold the last
one yet we'll wait for that Twitter
tweet to get a little bit of
okay maybe we need some pictures what
the Javan ji price is 275 all right guys
come on we got to sell one more
we got a literally sell one more get
your exclusive alright alright fine fine
fine I'm sold
I'm sold sure we dropped the price back
down a special price all right we're
gonna make a coupon code we're gonna
make a coupon code let's make your
coupon code that sounds great it's very
easy to do here on Shopify unless
somebody buys it before the coupon code
say last beanie you know why no no at
common hey I we only raised our prices
on hardware we don't lower our prices on
Hardware create discount we'll call it
okay bro 69 discount value is a fixed
amount it's ten dollars and it applies
to only the beanie
save discount
you got bad who's gonna buy the last
beanie there's literally one left guys
like I'll prove it to you I gotta I
gotta hide I gotta hide the rest of
these analytics but let me see if I can
only find the analytics for the beanie
Oh reports see reports oh we bring up a
live view yo the coupon codes posted on
Twitter the coupon codes posted on
Twitter okay bro 69
visitors right now in the store buy them
beanies right now let's go real-time
pages for a minute let's go we have 12
active cards nine people checking out
who's gonna get the BT five purchased
there's five purchase like I said
alright guys come on
who's gonna buy that last beanie who's
gonna turn that number to a six it can
be you there very nice exclusive comma
AI all black beanies no pictures you got
to come on periscope no okay bro 69 get
it right now buy that beanie buy that
beanie let's refresh this live view I
don't know if we have to refresh it oh
and is that 21 did I see 21 by the
beanie so good so I love it guys I love
it thank you for joining this comma AI
exclusive merch dropped beanie ship on
Monday love to all the scope is comma AI
wear the most lip self-driving car team
in the world back on that logan paul buy
my march but you can't cuz it's sold out
six beanies thank you for joining